Mykyta Korba

Front-end Developer

KYIV, UKRAINE NO.KORBA@GMAIL.COM +380961800636

SUMMARY

As a Software developer, I'm specialized in writing quality code either starting a new project from scratch or getting into an existent one in the middle of the road.

I have good knowledge of front-end development process and hope to share my skills, expertise and experience with my team. I have strong analytical skills, which allow me to find decisions by consistent analysis of problems. Based on my technical education I hope to use my knowledge to perform any development activities

EMPLOYMENT

JUL 2020 - AUG 2021

Front-end Developer, Avalog

An application that automates a full, client-focused investment process to strengthen and streamline advisory and discretionary business. A unified platform combines four applications tailored to financial specialists. Investment analysts, portfolio managers, advisors and relationship managers collaborate via appealing interfaces that produce coherent strategies, personalized portfolios and timely advice for clients along a seamless investment journey. A unified data model ensures that data stays consistent, actions taken transparent and operational risk in check.

Responsibilities:

- Work closely with clients to establish problem specifications and system designs.
- Implementing new functionality

Tools and technologies: Angular, NX, NgRx, Angular Material, Lodash, Ramda, Angular Schematics, MomentJS, Swagger, TSlint, ESLint, Jenkins, Git(BitBucket)

MAR 2020 - JUL 2020

Front-end Developer, Otalio

Shipboard property management system for all aspects of onboard operations with large palette of functionalities including application for Spa, Dining and Events Management, Excursions, Housekeeping and Maintenance, Gangway control, Safety and Security. Incorporates Point-of-Sales within its attributes, enabling real-time transfer of package consumption onto passenger accounts without the need of further integration effort. Detailed crew handling including safety courses and certificates, medical exam records, crew effects and activity. Flexible tool, allowing teams to update set-up data as well as controlling financial aspects of onboard operations.

Responsibilities:

- Implementing new functionality
- Writing documentation
- Scrum master

Tools and technologies: Angular, NX, Bootstrap, Angular Material, Angular Schematics, MomentJS, GraphQL, Swagger, TSlint, Jenkins, Git(BitBucket)

FEB 2018 -MAR 2020

Front-end Developer, Solarwinds

A framework with decent amount of UI components that are used by the

large network monitoring platform and integrated into a lot of modules within it. This application is based on AngularJS and Angular and includes activities like making sure that framework can easily be consumed, documentation is well written, test coverage and code quality are on a decent level. Besides that there is also a consumer application based on MEAN stack with Docker. This application acts as a testing ground to check latest release changes.

Responsibilities:

- Writing unit tests
- Writings E2E tests
- · Implementing new functionality
- Migrating components from AngularJS to Angular
- Writing documentation

Tools and technologies:

Angular, AngularJS, D3, Lodash, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Gulp, TypeScript, Karma, TSlint, TeamCity, Git(BitBucket), Docker, Applitools

DEC 2017 - JAN 2018

Front-end Developer, Swipeln

HR management system that suggests you the best candidates for your vacancies based on commuting distance, skills match %, availability and even security clearance status.

Responsibilities:

• Implementing new functionality and rewriting the old one

Tools and technologies: Angular 4, NodeJS, Express, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Parse SDK, Git (Bitbucket).

JUN 2017 -OCT 2017

Front-end Developer, Foodbucket

FoodBucket is an application for ordering food, where you can see the ingredients of a dish and can order either the cooked dish or just the ingredients to cook them yourself.

Responsibilities:

- Implementing backend API using Swagger and NodeJS
- Creating routing and navigation
- Created wireframes and front end implementations for several application pages

Tools and technologies: Angular 4, NodeJS, Express, Swagger, TypeScript, ES6, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Mongoose, Webpack, Jasmine, Jira, Git (Gitlab).

EDUCATION

SEP 2015 - JUN 2017

Master's degree, Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

Faculty of cybernetics. Applied mathematics

CERTIFICATES

JAN 2020

Microsoft

Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3